(Penny:)Oh, which one?
(Penny:)Maybe we can get Amy to try it.
(Bernadette:)I don't know.
(Bernadette:)Stuart, can you come in here?
(Bernadette:)He tried to explain it to me.
(Bernadette:)It shows you pictures
of people nearby,
(Bernadette:)you swipe them around,
it looks kind of like a game.
(Penny:)Oh, and if you lose the game,
you have to go out with Stuart.
(Stuart:)What's up?
(Bernadette:)Can you show us that dating app?
(Stuart:)Oh, yeah, sure.
(Stuart:)This thing has changed my life.
(Penny:)Wow. So how many
girls have you met?
(Stuart:)Two.
(Stuart:)I probably don't need to mention
(Stuart:)there's an entire number
between that and zero.
(Penny:)Well, so how
does it work?
Uh, well, it-it shows me all
(Stuart:)the single women
in a five-mile radius
(Stuart:)who are using the app.
(Stuart:)If I like the way they look,
I hit “thumbs up.”
If I don't, “thumbs down.”
(Bernadette:)Oh, what would make you
give a girl a thumbs down?
(Stuart:)First time it happens
I will let you know.
(Leonard:)Oh, hey. I just heard back
from the liquid helium guy.
(Sheldon:)What's he say?